Guide to the Division of Academic Affairs Records RG 6
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Division of Academic Affairs Records
1904-2014
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Western Connecticut State University. Division of Academic Affairs.
RG 6
20 Linear Feet 28 Boxes
The role of the the Division of Academic Affairs has evolved in name and purpose over the history of the WCSU. Currently the division is headed by the V.P. of Academic Affairs & Provost. The Division of Academic Affairs collection includes: administrative records, accreditation records, admissions data, institutional research and assessment records, and strategic planning information.
Provenance
Transferred to the WCSU Archives from 2000-2004, with accretions thereafter.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
The role of the the Division of Academic Affairs has evolved in name and purpose over the history the history of the school. Currently the division is headed by the V.P. of Academic Affairs & Provost. It works closely with the deans of the schools, the registrar’s office, the enrollment department officer, the director of the library and the grants director to serve the undergraduate and graduate community in development of curriculum and faculty, outreach to the community, research opportunities, statewide projects to develop educational opportunities and programs.
Scope and Content Note
Series 1 contains Academic Planning Calendars for faculty and staff that contain dates for faculty meetings, deadlines for grades, course offerings, and committee reports, and ceremonies for faculty and staff. Student Academic Calendars contain dates for registration, freshmen orientation, holidays, grades and exams. Researchers should note that academic calendars are also in the university's Course Catalogs. Faculty Guidelines give an overall view of campus facilities and academic policies and procedures.
Series 1 also contains most of the materials original processed as the Academic Programs Records (formerly RG6). Sub-series 1: Ancell School of Business, 1973-2001; Box 1; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order; Annual reports, manual, MSA and MBA chronologies, course outlines, newsletter, and pamphlets.
Sub-series 2: Arts and Sciences, School of, 1933-2000; Box 1-2; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order; Graduate and undergraduate course outlines, degree programs, syllabi, health education pamphlets, Interim Program, pamphlets and flyers.
Sub-series 3: Division of Graduate Studies and External Programs, 1955-2000; Box 2; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order; Courses Abroad and Waterbury programs.
Sub-series 4: Faculty, 1919-2003; Box 2-3; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order; Evaluations, rosters, workshops, directories, and publications.
Sub-series 5: School of Professional Studies, 1919-2002; Box 3-4; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order; Correspondence, minutes, reports, and course outlines.
Series 2 contains institutional and program specific reports, self-assessment, evaluations, and correspondence related to the accreditation process. Specific self-assessment reports for programs and departments can be found in sub-series Academic Planning Steering Committee, Ancell School of Business, CSDE, Institutional Research & Assessment, NEASC, and the School of Professional Studies.
Of particular importance is the fifth year interim report acceptance letter from the NEASC dated November 11, 1998, which contains recommendations in preparation for the comprehensive evaluation scheduled for the year 2003 with emphasis to steps the University has taken to incorporate the contributions of minorities and women.
The series also includes bound editions of Graduate Council Minutes, Graduate Committee minutes and matriculation reports.
Series 3 contains correspondence with prospective students seeking admission to the teaching program during 1904-1912. In addition, State Board of Education correspondence regarding admission, certification, and placement are also included. Publications originating from the Office of Admissions are also included.
Series 4 contains student surveys that give characteristics of full-time, part-time undergraduates, and part-time graduate students. Enrollment Reports include freshman profiles as well as CSU statistics and preliminary discussions regarding a statewide recruiting plan for WCSU.
Series 5 contains information on the Ruth A. Haas and Robert S. Young Libraries. Circulation records for 1919-1976 are handwritten in ledger form and are broken down by discipline using the Dewey Decimal System of classification. Architectural drawings and blueprints for the library renovation and addition, as well as for the "Swing Space," are also included. The Swing Space, which was temporary housing for the library during the renovation, has been renamed Warner Hall in honor of the late Truman A. Warner, Jr., professor emeritus.
Series 6 contains information related to Media Services and the availability of audio-visual equipment and supplies for use in the classrooms. The bulk of the materials in this series are newsletters, inventories and annual reports that cover 1937-1963.
Series 7 documents Strategic Planning activities during the 1990s. The Master Plan compiled by Dober, Lidsky, Craig and Associates, Inc., gave the Strategic Plan a physical definition by describing the physical resources that existed, the additional facilities that were needed, and how the University foresaw creating them. The Program for the Master Plan, which was a related study designed to show the physical and programmatic implications of the Strategic Plan, summarized the current and projected facility needs for WCSU, and provided the University with a framework for making day-to-day decisions on space allocation, building renovation, and site and infrastructure improvements.
Series 8 contains materials relating to Adult and Continuing Education such as course offerings, materials from the Connecticut Association of Continuing Education, the Connecticut State Department of Education and the American Association of State Colleges and Universities.
Series 9 is Course Materials. The materials in this series document different course and program offerings, as well as the modification, deletion, and addition of courses and programs.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically in each series by topic
The files are grouped into 9 series.
Missing Title
1.Administration
2.Accreditation
3.Admissions
4.Institutional Research and Assessment
5.Library Services
6.Media Services
7.Strategic Planning
8.Continuing and Adult Education
9. Course Materials
Related material
Up until 2016 RG 6 (formerly Academic Programs) and RG 6a (formerly Academic Affairs) were listed as seperate collections. These 2 record groups now have been realigned and processed as the Division of Academic Affairs Records.
Directories.; Photographs.; Library planning -- Connecticut.; Universities and colleges -- Administration.; Correspondence.; Reports.; Accreditation (Education) -- Connecticut -- Danbury; Libraries -- Connecticut.; Connecticut. State Library Board.; Galliher, Baier, and Best.; Stevens, Norman D.; Western Connecticut State University -- Accreditation.; Western Connecticut State University. Division of Academic Affairs.
- Series 1. Administration
  - General
    - Academic Planning Summary, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5a)
      General
      Copy left on reserve at the Haas Library, Oct 2000 by VP Buccini. Added 12/2011
    - Center for Excellence in Teaching and Learning, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1996-2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Guidelines, 1987-2004 (Box 1, Folder 8-21)
    - Faculty Guidelines (copy 2), 1989-1998 (Box 9, Folder 47-49)
    - "From the Paris Conservataory to Dublin: Flutes and Voices, April 11, 2005" (Box 9, Folder 45)
      One CD
    - "A Celebration of Spring, Dedicated to the memory of Ernest R. Machell, Jr., April 26, 2004" (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Academic Planning Calendar, 1987-1998 (Box 1, Folder 3-5)
    - Academic Calendar, 2000- (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Academic Calendar, 1970-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Departmental Minutes/Correspondence - acc 2010.020
    General note
    2010 accession (acc # 2010.020)
    - Department of Arts - Administration, 1995-2007 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Department of Arts - Minutes, 1999-2005 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Department of Biology - External Review, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Department of Biology - Minutes, 1995-1999 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Department of Biology - Minutes, 2000-2004 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Department of Biology - Minutes, 2005-2007 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Department of Chemistry - Letters/Correspondence, 1992-1997 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Department of Chemistry - Letters/Correspondence, 1997-2006 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Department of Chemistry - Minutes, 1998-2004 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Department of Education - Letters/Correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Department of Education - Letters/Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Department of Education - Letters/Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Department of Education - Minutes, 1995-2007 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Department of English - Letters/Correspondence/Memos, 1995-1999 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Department of English - Letters/Correspondence/Memos, 2000-2002 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Department of English - Letters/Correspondence/Memos, 2005-2007 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Department of English - Minutes, 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Department of English - Minutes, 1999-2004 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Department of English - Minutes, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Department of Finance - Minutes, 1992-2005 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Department of History - Non Western Culture - Letters/Correspondence, 1991-1999 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Department of History - Non Western Culture - Minutes, 1995-1999 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Department of History - Non Western Culture - Minutes, 2000-2006 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Department of Justice & Law - Letters/Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Department of Justice & Law - Letters/Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Department of Justice & Law - Letters/Correspondence, 2001-2007 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Department of Justice & Law - Minutes, 1994-2006 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Department of Management - Minutes, 1992-2000 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Department of Management - Minutes, 2001-2004 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Department of Management - Minutes, 2005-2007 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Department of Management, 1994-2001 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Department of Nursing - Letters/Correspondence/Memos, 2006-2007 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Department of Nursing - Letters/Correspondence/Memos, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Department of Nursing - Minutes, 2002-2007 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Department of Physics & Astronomy - Letters/Correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Department of Physics & Astronomy - Letters/Correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Department of Physics & Astronomy - Minutes, 2000-2006 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Department of Psychology - Letters/Correspondence, 2000-2005 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Department of Psychology - Letters/Correspondence, 1994-1999 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Department of Psychology - Minutes, 2000-2007 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Department of Psychology - Minutes, 1992-1999 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Department of Social Science - Letters/Correspondence, 1995-2006 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Department of Social Science - Minutes, 1993-2006 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Department of Social Work - Letters/Correspondence, 1993-2007 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Department of Social Work - Minutes, 2000-2007 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Department of World Languages & Literature - Notes, 2004-2006 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Department of World Languages & Literature - Notes, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Departmental Annual Reports
    - 1996-1997
      - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Arts and Science - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Arts and Science - Art, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Arts and Science - Communication and Theatre Arts, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Arts and Science - Biological and Environmental Sciences, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Arts and Science - Chemistry, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Arts and Science - English, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Arts and Science - Foreign Languages and Literature, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Arts and Science - History and Non-Western Cultures, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Arts and Science - Mathematics and Computer Science, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Arts and Science - Philosophy and Humanistic Studies, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Arts and Science - Psychology, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Arts and Science - University Scholars Program, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Arts and Science - Social Sciences, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - Arts and Sciences, 2007-2008; CD-RW (Box 21, Folder 45)
      - Professional Studies - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Professional Studies - Education and Educational Psychology, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      - Professional Studies - Music and Music Education, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      - Professional Studies - Health Science, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Professional Studies - Nursing, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 19)
      - Professional Studies - Physical Education, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      - Professional Studies - Social Work, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      - Ancell - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Ancell - Accounting, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 23)
      - Ancell - Finance, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 24)
      - Ancell - Justice and Law Administration, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 25)
      - Ancell - Management, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 26)
      - Ancell - Management Information Systems, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 27)
      - Ancell - Marketing, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 28)
      - Athletics - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 29)
      - Weather Center - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 30)
      - Admissions and Graduate Studies - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 31)
      - Academic Advising Center - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 32)
      - Institutional Research and Assessment - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 33)
      - Media Services - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 34)
      - Human Resources Management - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 35)
      - Academics Information Technology Center - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 36)
      - Department of Housing and Residence Life - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 37)
      - Faith Communities - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 38)
      - Minority Affairs - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 39)
      - Financial Aid - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 40)
      - Counseling Center - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 41)
      - Career Development Center - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 42)
      - Health Services - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 43)
      - Student and External Affairs - Overview, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - 1997 - 1998
      - Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Institutional Advancement - Overview, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Academic Affairs - Overview, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Finance and Administration - Overview, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Student Affairs (1 of 2) - Overview, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Student Affairs (2/2) - Overview, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Arts and Science - Academic Advisement Center, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Ancell - Overview, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Ancell - Accounting, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Ancell - Finance, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Ancell - Justice and Law Administration, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Ancell - Management, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Ancell - Management Information Systems, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Ancell - Marketing, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Ancell - Masters of Business Administration/Masters of Health Administration, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - Professional Studies - Overview, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Professional Studies - Education and Educational Psychology, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - Professional Studies - Health Science, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Professional Studies - Music and Music Education, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Professional Studies - Nursing, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - Professional Studies - Physical Education, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - Professional Studies - Social Work, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - 1998 - 1999
      - Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - Executive Summary - Overview, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Ancell - Overview, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - Ancell - Finance, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - Ancell - Justice and Law Administration, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 27)
      - Ancell - Management, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - Arts and Science - Overview, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - Arts and Science - Art, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 30)
      - Arts and Science - Biological and Environmental Sciences, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 31)
      - Arts and Science - Chemistry, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 32)
      - Arts and Science - Communications and Theatre Art, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 33)
      - Arts and Science - English, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 34)
      - Arts and Science - Forign Languages and Literature, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 35)
      - Arts and Science - History and Non-Western Cultures, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 36)
      - Arts and Science - Mathematics and Computer Science, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 37)
      - Arts and Science - Philosophy & Humanistic Studies, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 38)
      - Arts and Science - Physics, Astronomy and Meteorology, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 39)
      - Arts and Science - Psychology, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 40)
      - Arts and Science - Social Sciences, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 41)
      - Arts and Science - University Scholars, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 42)
      - Arts and Science - Academic Advisement Center, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Arts and Science - Learning Labs, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Arts and Science - Weeather Center, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Office of Institutional Research and Assessment, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Libraries - Overview, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Professional Studies - Overview, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - University Computing - Overview, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - 1999 - 2000
      - Overview, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Ancell - Overview, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Ancell - Accounting, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Ancell - Finance, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Ancell - Justice and Law Administration, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Ancell - Management, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Ancell - Management Information Systems, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Ancell - Markting, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Ancell - Master of Business Administration / Master of Health Administration, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Ancell - Masters of Justice and Law Administration, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Advisement Center - Overview, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Arts and Sciences - Overview, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - Arts and Sciences - Art, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Arts and Sciences - Biological and Environmental Sciences, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Arts and Sciences - Chemistry, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Arts and Sciences - Communication and Theatre Arts, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Arts and Sciences - English, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Arts and Sciences - Forign Languages and Literature, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Arts and Sciences - History and Non-Western Cultures, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Arts and Sciences - Mathematics and Computer Science, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Arts and Sciences - Philosophy and Humanistic Studies, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Arts and Sciences - Physics, Astronomy and Meteorology, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Arts and Sciences - Psychology, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Arts and Sciences - Social Sciences, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - Arts and Sciences - Univrsity Scholars, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - Arts and Sciences - Academic Advisement Center, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - Arts and Sciences - Weather Center, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - International Center - Overview, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - Institutional Research and Assessment - Overview, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - Libraries - Overview, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 37)
      - Media Services - Overview, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 38)
      - Professional Studies - Overview, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 39)
      - Professional Studies - Health Science, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - 2001 - 2002
      - Ancell - Overview, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 41)
      - WCSU/CCSU at Waterbury - Overview, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - 2004 - 2005
      - Ancell - Overview, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 43)
      - Ancell - Accounting, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 44)
      - Ancell - Finance, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 45)
      - Ancell - Justice and Law Administration, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 46)
      - Ancell - Management, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 47)
      - Ancell - Management Information Systems, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 48)
      - Ancell - Marketing, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 49)
      - Ancell - Masters of Business Administration, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 50)
      - Ancell - Masters of Health Administration, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 51)
      - Ancell - Masters of Science in Justice and Law Administration, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 52)
      - School of Arts & Science: Advertising Center Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_1_x (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - School of Arts & Science: Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_2_x (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - School of Arts & Science: Art Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_3_x (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - School of Arts & Science: Biology Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_4_x (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - School of Arts & Science: Chemistry Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_5_x (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - School of Arts & Science: Commuincations Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_6_x (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - School of Arts & Science: Computer Science Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_7_x (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - School of Arts & Science: English Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_8_x (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - School of Arts & Science: Honors Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_9_x (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - School of Arts & Science: History Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_10_x (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - School of Arts & Science: Mathematics Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_11_x (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - School of Arts & Science: Philosophy Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_12_x (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - School of Arts & Science: Physics & Astonomy Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_13_x (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - School of Arts & Science: Psychology Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_14_x (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - School of Arts & Science: Social Science Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_15_x (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - School of Arts & Science: Theatre Arts Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_16_x (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - School of Arts & Science: Weather Center Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_17_x (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - School of Arts & Science: Westside Nature Preserve Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_18_x (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - School of Arts & Science: World Languages Annual Report, 2004-2005; RG6.xx_10_19_x (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - 2005 - 2006